瑞秋 我们这边履历表快用完了
Rach, we're running low on resumes over here.
你真的想去《大众机械师》杂志社做事吗
Do you really want a job with ?
要是想为机械师做点事 那儿倒是不错的选择
Well, if you're gonna work for mechanics, those are the ones to work for.
说真的 我什么都要试试
Hey, look, you guys, I'm going for anything here, okay?
我不想再当服务生了 真的
I can not be a waitress anymore. I mean it.
我已经厌倦了那点微薄的小费
I'm sick of the lousy tips.
厌倦了总是被叫"劳驾"
I'm sick of being called "Excuse Me".
瑞秋 你写完后 有检查过吗
Rach, did you proofread these?
有啊 怎么了
Uh, yeah. Why?
没什么 你优秀的电"恼"能力
Uh, nothing. I'm sure they'll be impressed
我相信大家都会印象深刻
with your excellent "compuper" skills.
我的天
Oh, my God!
每一份上面都是这样吗
Oh, do you think it's on all of them?
不会啦 我相信影印机一定帮你抓住一些了
Oh, no, I'm sure the Xerox machine caught a few.
【海盗美剧 友情制作】
-== http://www.hdmeiju.com ==-
新浪微博：@海盗美剧
《老友记》蓝光版 第01季 第18集
扑克风波 The One With All The Poker
调校制作：寒 枫
字幕编辑：小龟快快跑
大家好      嘿
Hey, guys.        Hey.
嗨 两位小姐
Hey! Hi, ladies!
需要些什么吗
Uh, can I get you anything?
信带来了吗      很多回复
Did you bring the mail?        Lots of responses.
真的吗 我们这儿当然还有烤饼
Really? Sure we have scones left.
好 快念给我听听
Okay, read them to me.
亲爱的葛林小姐 谢谢您的申请 不过…
"Dear Miss Green: Thank you for your inquiry, however..."
我们有苹果肉桂
We have apple cinnamon...
亲爱的葛林小姐
Okay, "Dear Miss Green"
好 好 好 不行
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. No.
哇喔        什么啊
Wow!        What?
你的卡债还真多
Your Visa bill is huge.
拿来
Give me that.
我真不敢相信
You know, I can't believe you.
琳达那么好 你为什么不再约她出去了
Linda is so great. Why won't you go out with her again?
我也说不清
I don't know.
难道还是因为
Is this still about her whole
她认为"摩登原始人"真可能发生
"The Flintstones could have really happened" thing?
不只是那样
It's not just that.
我只是想要一个能让我有感觉
It's just, I want someone who does something for me...
让我心跳加速
you know, who gets my heart pounding,
让我
who makes me, uh...
成为拜倒在石榴裙下的玩物
Little play things with yarn?
什么啊
What?
还有谁比她更让你心动
Could you want her more?
谁
Who?
蒂 肥皂剧《发生何事》里的那个尖酸刻薄的女生
Dee, the sarcastic sister from !
我对她已经完全没有感觉了 行吗
Look, I am totally totally over her, okay?
我只是 嗨      嗨 还要咖啡吗
I just... Hi!        Hi! Coffee?
不了 这样就好      好
No, we're fine.         Okay.
哈哈哈
Hah hah hah!
闭嘴
Shut up!
我们什么都没说哦
We're not saying anything.
什么啊
What?
乔伊昨晚哭了
Uh, Joey cried last night.
谢谢
Thank you.
我们不是在玩牌吗
We were playing poker, right?
3上面沾了点巧克力 看起来像是个8
There was chocolate on the three. It looked like an eight, all right?
可惜你们没看到他说 "开牌 你们准备哭吧"
Oh, God, you should've seen him. "Read them and weep".
结果哭的是他
And then he did.
为什么你们从没和我们玩过牌
Well, now, how come you guys have never played poker with us
对啊 为什么 就好像这是男生的专利
Yeah, what is that? Like some kind of guy thing?
是有性别歧视的男生的专利
Like some kind of sexist guy thing?
这是扑克牌 所以只有男生能玩
Like, it's poker, so only guys can play?
不啊 我们也很欢迎女生玩
No. Women are welcome to play.
那么到底是为什么
Oh, okay, so then what is it?
就好像... 就好像...
Some kind of, you know, like, some kind of, you know, like...
算了 到底是怎样
All right, what is it?
只是刚好我们玩牌时没有女生加入而已
There just don't happen to be any women in our game.
对啊 我们只是不认识会玩扑克牌的女生
Yeah, we just don't happen to know any women that know how to play poker.
拜托 这个借口真烂 典型的男生答案
Oh, please, that is such a lame excuse. I mean, it's a typical guy response.
对不起 你们当中有人会玩吗
Excuse me, do any of you know how to play?
不会
No.
但是你们可以教我们
But you could teach us.
不要
No.
好 现在我们抽牌
Okay, so now we draw cards.
我不需要再抽了吧  我有个顺子
So I wouldn't need any, right? Because I have a straight.
太好了      恭喜你
Oh, good for you!        Congratulations!
好吧 菲比 你要几张
Okay, Pheebs, how many do you want?
我要两张
Okay, I just need two.
黑桃10跟梅花6
The ten of spades and the six of clubs.
不行 菲比 不可以这样
No, uh, Pheebs, you can't do that.
噢 我有黑桃10 你要不要
Ooh! I have the ten of spades. Here, you want it?
谢谢
Thanks.
不行 不可以这样子
Uh, no, see, uh, you can't do that.
没关系 我不需要那些
No, no, no. That's okay. That's okay. I don't need them.
我需要的是4
I'm going for fours.
啊 你在
Oh, you're...
好 吃的来啦
All right, here we go.
这是鲑鱼拼盘和什锦水果
We've got salmon roulettes and assorted crudites.
摩妮卡 你在干什么
Whoa, whoa, whoa. Monica, what are you doing?
我们在玩扑克牌
This is a poker game.
所有食物的名字不能超过一个词
You can't serve food with more than one syllable.
像薯片 蘸汁 脆饼
It's got to be like chips or dip or pretz.
好 现在庄家
Okay, so at this point, the dealer...
好了 我们会了 我们会了
You know what? We got it. We got it.
开始玩真的吧 高风险 玩真钱
Let's play for real, right? High stakes. Big bucks.
你确定吗 菲比刚丢出两张杰克
All right, now, you sure? Phoebe just threw away two jacks...
因为它们看起来很不快乐
because they didn't look happy.
但是我准备好了 发牌吧
But I'm ready. So just deal.
好 最后一课 最后一课
Okay, all right, last minute lesson, last minute lesson.
乔伊 这是3
Joey. Three
这是8
Eight
8  3 好了 可以开始了
Eight, three. All right. Here we go.
该死 该死 该死
Damn it, damn it, damn it!
我知道了 原来你是在说谎
I see. So then, urn, you were lying.
说什么谎了
About what?
说你的牌有多好
About how good your cards were.
那叫做唬人
I was bluffing.
啊哈 那唬人是什么
Aha. And what is "bluffing"?
不就是说谎吗
Is it not another word for lying?
好了 不能再玩了
Okay, sorry to break up this party...
我得在明天上班前把履历表发出去
but I've go resumes to fax before work tomorrow.
瑞秋 瑞秋 我们得定局
Rach, Rach, we've got to settle.
定什么局
Settle what?
维吉尼亚州詹姆士镇的殖民地
The Jamestown colony of Virginia.
乔治国王给我们那块地 所以...
You see, King George is giving us the land, so...
瑞秋 是赌局
The game, Rachel, the game.
赌局里你欠我们钱
You owe us money for the game.
对哦
Oh, right.
这样吧 这是她们第一次玩牌
You know what, guys? It's their first time.
我们就算了好不好
Why don't we just forget about the money?
才不要 我们会付的
Hell, no, we'll pay.
摩妮卡 我本来已经准备好了另一个答案
Okay, Monica, I had another answer all ready.
这样好了
And you know what?
我们再来一场
We want a rematch.
我没问题
Well, that's fine with me.
我可以用赢的这些钱
Could use the money.
这么说基本上 你们通过赢朋友的钱来过瘾的
So, basically, you get your yayas by taking money from all of your friends.
没错      对 我靠上宜家过瘾
Yeah.        Yes, and I get my yayas from Ikea.
你得自己组装那些家具 但是会便宜一点
You have to put them together yourself but they cost a little less.
瑞秋 我玩扑克牌的目的 就是想赢 好吗
Look Rachel, this is poker. I play to win, all right?
我要赢 别人就得输
In order for me to win, other people have to lose.
你要跟我玩扑克牌
So if you're gonna play poker with me,
就别指望我手下留情
don't expect me to be a nice guy.
因为只要一发牌
Okay, because once those cards are dealt..
怎样
Yeah?
我就六亲不认
I'm not a nice guy.
好了 有东西吃了
All right, boys. Let's eat.
你是在"我爱瑞秋"披萨店买的吗
Ah, did you get that from the "I Love Rachel" pizzeria?
你还在想那个
You still on that?
拜托 那个学黑社会讲话是怎么回事
Come on. What was with that whole Black Bad speech?
一玩扑克牌 我就六亲不认
"When I play poker, I'm not a nice guy"
老兄 你大错特错了
You're way off, pal.
我可不这么认为 罗斯 因为我认为你爱她
No I don't think so, see Ross, because I think you love her.
没有
Uh, no.
我或许曾经对她有过好感
See, I might have had feelings for her at one time.
但那都过去了
Not anymore.
我只是
I just...
马塞尔 你拿那张光碟干什么
Marcel, where are you going with that disk?
不可以再放了
You are not putting that on again.
马塞尔 敢按下那个键
Marcel, okay. If you press that button,
你就完蛋了
you are in very very big trouble.
你能相信罗斯居然那么浑蛋吗
You believe what a jerk Ross was being?
我知道 他还真是很好胜
Yeah I know. He can get really competitive.
啊 哈哈
Ah hah hah!
干嘛啊
What?
摩妮卡 你是五十步笑百步吧
"Hello,Kettle, this is Monica. You're black."
拜托
Please!
我没有像罗斯那么糟
I am not as bad as Ross.
抱歉 我看不出差别 记得画图猜谜事件吗
Oh, I beg to differ. The Pictionary incident?
那不是什么事件
That was not an incident.
我正在比划 盘子就从我手里溜出去了
I was gesturing and the plate slipped out of my hand.
我有面试了      真的吗
Oh! I got an interview.        You're kidding.
我有面试了      哪里
I got an interview.        Where?
萨克斯百货公司 第五大街      哇 瑞秋
Saks Fifth Avenue.        Oh Rachel!
这就好像母舰在召你归队
Oh, it's like the mother ship is calling you home.
是什么样的职位      采购助理
Well, what's the job?        Assistant buyer.
我可以靠血拼
Oh! I would be shopping...
来谋生了
for a living.
好 爱瑞丝阿姨来了
Okay, look, that's Aunt Iris.
她5岁就开始玩扑克牌了
This woman has been playing poker since she was five.
她说的每一个字都要注意听
You've gotta listen to every word she says.
你好      喜剧泰斗东尼蓝道死了吗
Hi!        Is Tony Randall dead?
怎么会      我没听说
Oh, why?        I don't think so.
他现在可能已经死了
Well, he may be now.
因为我好像开车撞到他了
because I think I hit him with my car.
我的天 真的吗
My God! Really?
假的 第一课 这就是唬人
No, that's bluffing. Lesson number one.
告诉你们吧
Let me tell you something.
在牌桌上听到的 通通不可以当真
Everything you hear at a poker game is pure crap.
好漂亮的耳环      谢…
Nice earrings.        Thank you.
各位小姐 坐下
Girls, sit down.
爱瑞丝阿姨 这是菲比 瑞秋      好了 好了 好了
Urn, Aunt Iris, this is Phoebe, and Rachel...        Yeah, yeah, yeah.
我们赶紧开始吧 这里停车要计时收费
Listen, I am parked at a meter. Let's do it.
罗斯 拜托 我们能不能听点别的
Ross, could we please, please, please listen to anything else?
好吧
All right.
今晚我完蛋了
I'm gonna pay for that tonight.
嗨      你好
Hi.         Hey.
你们猜 你们猜 你们猜
Guys, guess what, guess what, guess what.
嗯 第五个牙医也屈服了
Uh, okay. The fifth dentist caved.
现在他们都开始推荐薄荷口香糖了
And now they're all recommending Trident?
不是 是我的面试
No, the interview.
她好喜欢我 超级喜欢我
She loved me. She absolutely loved me.
我们谈了两个半小时
We talked for, like, two and a half hours.
我们的衣着品味相同
We have the same taste in clothes.
我跟她表妹还去过同一个夏令营
Oh, I went to camp with her cousin.
这工作太完美了
And, oh, the job is perfect.
我可以做得很好  一定可以
I can do this. I can do this well.
太好了
That's great.
而且她的故事超好笑的
God! And she told the funniest story.
好极了 你说出来 我们一定会笑的
Okay, great. You'll tell us and we'll laugh.
开始玩牌吧
Let's play poker.
好 我们谈过了
All right, listen you guys, we talked about it.
如果你们不想玩 我们完全理解
And if you don't want to play, we completely understand.
对 我们可以玩别的 像是
Yes, yes. We can play some other game. Like, I don't know...
画图猜谜
Pictionary?
很好笑 很好笑
Very funny. Very funny.
我们再给扑克牌一次机会吧 好吗 两位小姐
But I think we'd like to give poker another try. Shall we, ladies?
好啊      好啊 没问题
Yes!        I think we should.
瑞秋 要我洗牌吗
Rach, do you want me to shuffle those?
不用了 没关系
No. no, that's okay.
我想自己试试
You know what? I'm gonna give it a go.
好吧      好吧
All right.        All right.
菲比欠7块5 摩妮卡 你欠10块
So Pheebs owes $7.50. Monica, you owe $10.
瑞秋 你欠15块
And, Rachel, you owe 15 big ones.
谢谢你们教我们斜眼玛丽
Thanks for teaching us "Crossed eyed Mary."
我们自己玩的时候也可以用
You guys, we gotta play that other way.
7块5拿去 你们要知道 这钱被诅咒了
All right, here's my $7.50. But I think you should know that this money is cursed.
什么      哦 诅咒是我下的
What?        Oh, I cursed it.
谁花掉这些钱 谁就会倒霉的
So now bad things will happen to he who spends it.
没关系 给我吧 反正我一直都很倒霉
Thats all right, I'll take it. Bad things happen to me anyway.
这样我就可以用电影解除咒语
This way, I can break them up with a movie.
现在只剩下葛林扑克牌机了 她欠我们15块
So that just leaves the big Green poker machine, who owes $15.
简直就是典型的…
Hmm, oh, it's so typical:
我是个男人 我是带把的
"Ooh, I'm a man. Ooh, I have a penis.
我就是要通过赢钱来显示出驾驭女性的能力
Ooh, I have to win money to exert my power over women."
你们知道吗 我们还没玩完
You know what? This is not over.
我们会再来找你们
We will play you again.
我们将会赢 你们将会输
And we will win and you will lose.
你们将会求饶 我们则会讥笑你们
And you will beg and we will laugh.
我们会赢走你们身上的每一分钱
And we will take every last dime you have.
你们会永远恨死自己
And you will hate yourselves forever!
我们想法一致 摩妮卡
Hmm, kind of stepped on my point there, Mon.
你们要现在就付钱吗
So you gals wanna hand over your money now?
这样我们就可以直接跳过玩牌的仪式
That way, we don't have to go through the formality of actually playing.
不 我们倒要看看 到底谁能笑到最后 猴子男
No, that's fine. We'll see who has the last laugh there, monkey boy.
聊完了没有  可以开始认真打牌了吗
Okay, are we done with the chit chat? Are we ready to play serious poker?
你们看 单眼杰克的眼睛一直跟着我
Hey, you guys, look, the one eyed jack follows me wherever I go.
好吧 认真打牌
Right, okay. Serious poker！
不好意思 你要去哪里
Excuse me, where are you going?
上厕所
Uh, to the bathroom.
你是来上厕所 还是来玩扑克牌的
Do you wanna go to the bathroom or do you wanna play poker?
我想上厕所
I wanna go to the bathroom.
我打电话叫披萨外卖
All right, well, I'm gonna order a pizza.
不行 不行 不行 我在等那工作的面试结果
Oh, no, no, no. I'm still waiting to hear from that job.
百货公司9点关门 你那时候再吃吧
And the store closes at nine, so you can eat then.
那好吧 我先吃点薄荷糖垫垫肚子
That's fine. I'll just have a Tic Tac to hold me over.
好 辛辛那提扑克规则 不下盲注 大家先下注
All right. Cincinnati. No blinds. Everybody ante.
很好
Yes!
或是不好
Or no.
好了 你的钱就是我的 葛林
Alright! Your money's mine, Green.
你的拉链开着 盖勒
Your fly's open, Geller.
你们知道我刚想到什么吗
You guys, you know what I just realized?
杰克跟扑克只差一个字
"Joker" is "poker" with a "J".
很巧吧
Coincidence?
所以我们也可以叫它"杰"克牌
Hey, that's "joincidence" with a "C".
菲比 菲比      我不跟了
Uh, Phoebe, Phoebe?         Yeah,  I'm out.
我跟
I'm in.
我也跟
Me too.
我也跟 好 你是什么牌
Me too. All right. What do you got?
你最好离莲蓬头远一点 因为我的牌是同花
Well, you better hop out of the shower, because I got a flush.
呵 呵 呵
Well, well, well.
小子 别想逃 我有4张6
Hop back in, bucko, because I got four sixes.
我有4张6 我赢了 我真的赢了
I got four sixes. I won. I actually won.
天啊 你们知道吗  我要把小罗斯叠成一堆
Oh, my God! You know what? I think I'm gonna make a little Ross pile.
这是罗斯的 这也是罗斯的
I think that one was Ross'. And I think, oh, that one was Ross'.
你的钱是我的了 你再也看不到它了
Well, I have got your money. And you'll never see it.
你裤子的拉链还是开着
And your fly's still open.
哈 我让你低头看了
Hah, I made you look.
我跟
I'm in.
怎么可能不跟
I couldn't be inner.
摩妮卡  摩妮卡 你跟不跟
Monica? Monica, in or out?
我讨厌扑克牌
I hate this game.
好 乔伊 换你下注了
Okay, Joey, your bet.
我不来了 就像一个廉价妓女
I fold, like a cheap hooker who got hit in the stomach
被一个脸上流脓的胖子揍到肚子一样
by a fat guy with sores on his face.
不跟了
Oh, I'm out.
罗斯       我当然跟
Ross?        Oh, I'm very in.
钱德呢       怎么可能跟
Chandler?         Couldn't be more out.
我也不跟 瑞秋呢
Me too. Rachel?
我不但跟 而且还加注
Urn, I will see you and I'll raise you.
如何 想继续浪费钱吗
What do you say? You wanna waste another buck?
不了 这次不会
No, not this time.
你是什么牌       不告诉你
So, what did you have?         I'm not telling.
别这样 给我看看      不要
Come on, show them to me.        No.
给我看看 给我看看      手拿开 不给看
Show them to me. Let me see.        Get your hands out of there. No!
我有过这样的约会经验
You know, I've had dates like this.
老天 你就是输不起 对不对
Boy, you really can't stand to lose, can you?
你整个脸都涨红了
Your whole face is getting red.
太阳穴的青筋也爆出来了
Little veins popping out of your temple.
而且上衣跟裤子也不搭
Plus that shirt doesn't really match those pants.
首先 我没有输
First of all, I'm not losing.
发牌吧
Just deal.
喂 我是瑞秋葛林
Hello? Rachel Green.
请稍等一下
Excuse me.
这是有关工作的
It's about the job.
芭芭拉 嗨 你好
Barbara, hi! How are you?
啊哈 不 我了解
Aha! No. I understand.
喔 没关系 我很好 别傻了
Yeah, oh, come on. No, I'm fine. Don't be silly.
如果还有什么空缺 请…
Yeah. Oh, but you know, if anything else opens up, please...
喂
Hello?
我很遗憾 瑞秋
Sorry, Rach.
没关系 好工作满街都是
Yeah, you know, there's gonna be lots of other stuff.
是啊
Yeah. Okay.
我们玩到哪儿了 好
Where were we? Oh. Okay.
五张牌 11点或更高的
Five card draw. Uh, jacks are better
没有万能牌 大家下注吧
Nothing wild, everybody ante.
瑞秋 我们不用再玩下去了
Look, Rach, we don't have to do this.
当然要继续玩
Yes we do.
好 下注      下注
All right. Check.        Check.
我下5角钱
I'm in for 50 cents.
我跟      我跟
Call.         I'm in.
我跟你5角钱
I see your 50 cents.
然后加注 5块钱
And I raise you five dollars
我以为我们5角钱是上限
I thought, uh, it was a 50 cent limit.
我刚刚失去一份工作 我想加注5块钱
Well, I just lost a job, and I'd like to raise the bet 5 bucks.
有人有问题吗
Does anybody have a problem with that?
完全没有      没有 没有
Not at all.        No. no.
输家
Loser?
不了 我退出
No, I fold.
什么叫你退出  少来 这是干嘛
What do you mean, you fold? Hey, come on, what is this?
我还以为"一发牌 我就六亲不认"呢
I thought that, "Once the cards are dealt, I'm not a nice guy."
怎么 你只会说大话而已吗
I mean, what? Were you just full of it?
我跟
I'm in.
你要几张       一张
How many you want?         One.
庄家两张
Dealer takes two.
你下多少      两块
What do you bet?        I bet two dollars.
我跟你的两块
See your two.
然后加注 20块
And I raise you twenty.
哇
Wow!
我跟你的20
I see your twenty.
然后加注25块
Raise you twenty five.
我跟你的25块
See your twenty five.
摩妮卡 把我的钱包拿来
And, uh, Monica, get my purse.
瑞秋 里面没钱了
Rachel, there's nothing in it.
好 那就把你的拿来
Okay, then get me your purse.
好 拿去吧 祝你好运
Okay. Here you go. Good luck!
谢谢
Thank you.
我跟你的25块 然后加注 7块      再加10块
I saw your twenty five and I raise you seven...        teen.
乔伊 我囊中羞涩了
Joey, I'm a little shy.
没关系 罗斯 想问什么尽管问
That's okay, Ross. You can ask me.
你需要多少 需要多少      15块
What do you need? What do you need?        Fifteen.
这里有10块
All right, here's ten.
我有5块 5块钱
Here, I got five, I got five.
谢谢      祝你好运
Thank you.        Good luck.
好 跟你的17块
Okay, I am calling your seventeen.
亮牌吧
What do you got?
葫芦
Full house.
你赢了
You got me.
没关系 那很难赢
That's alright, y'know, that's a tough hand to beat.
我以为我们赢定了
I thought we had them.
没有好牌就是没有好牌 能怎么办
Well, when you don't have the cards, you don't have the cards, you know?
但是你们看她有多高兴
But look how happy she is.
航空信      飞机 机场
Airmail.        Airplane. Airport.
机场75 机场77 机场 79  (七十年代的系列电影)
Airport 75! Airport 77! Airport 79!
时间到
Time's up.
再见 伯蒂 (电影名 又译"欢乐今宵”)
Bye Bye Birdie
那是个鸟吗
That's a bird?
那是个鸟呀
That's a bird.
好了 好了 换我了
Okay, okay, it's my turn.
开始
Go.
豆子  豆子
Uh, Bean. Bean.
生命中不能承受之轻(又译"布拉格之恋")
The Unbearable Lightness of Being.
答对了
Yes!
这你就懂?
That you get?
【海盗美剧 友情制作】
-== http://www.hdmeiju.com ==-
新浪微博：@海盗美剧
海盗编号：HDT18-P1-24-18-01-1212